Maybe Asura is a shadow following you.
You’re just never aware of it.
This looks like a set up.
Don’t you feel that it’s too easy?
Stop protecting the murderer.
I’m not protecting the murderer.
I’m protecting what is right.
Dad?
You hate me, don’t you?
Since everything happened because of me,
I’ll be the one who ends it.
I can’t remember anything.
I don’t even know how I ended up there.
Did I kill them?
Am I a murderer?
Am I Nekros, Phat?
Phat.
You…
Did you get any sleep?
Why don’t you go wash your face
and freshen up?
I’ll make breakfast.
Oh, there’s a spare toothbrush
in the cabinet.
You can grab it from there.
Thanks.
I used to do this for my sister a lot.
So I know how to cook a little.
You should eat it while it’s hot.
Kaye.
The police are looking for you right now.
I turned off your phone.
Don’t turn it on.
Our IT team can definitely
track you down if you do.
I don’t get it.
Why me?
Who is the perfect scapegoat
for the murders
if not the creator like you?
But don’t worry.
I’ll do anything to prove
that you’re innocent.
So…
What can I do?
Just stay here.
Don’t go anywhere.
I’ll be back soon.
Okay?
Inspector.
We got the lab results for
the latent fingerprints in the crime scene.
The results show
Kaye’s fingerprints in many areas.
It’s enough to confirm he was at the scene
when the murder happened.
Did we find Inspector Phat?
Inspector Phat’s phone
has been off since last night.
Our cell site system still
hasn’t detected him.
I think he’s trying
to stay out of our radar.
If Inspector Phat chooses to take
the suspect’s side like this,
he is as good as obstructing
our investigation.
Seeing as he’s just disappeared,
why don’t you check out his place?
I’m worried about him.
Yes, sir.
You seem tense, Lieutenant.
Is everything alright?
Oh, I’m okay.
Let me know
if Inspector Phat contacts you.
Of course, sir.
Upload Kaye’s profile
onto our suspect database.
I want all police precincts in the country
to have this information.
Yes, sir.
Inspector.
How did you get in here?
Drive.
Sir.
Kaye won’t make it out of this.
Inspector Kitti just added Kaye
to the nation-wide suspect database.
Every cop is—
I said drive.
Sir.
Did you not hear me?
Drive.
Yes, sir.
I turned off your phone.
Don’t turn it on.
(Our IT team can definitely
track you down if you do.)
Clear.
Hey. Over here.
Come on.
Halt!
Breaking News.
The police have issued an arrest warrant
for Chankacha Thanyapat,
the creator of Nekros,
(the suspect in the serial murders,
who is currently running.)
(The suspect is deemed dangerous
and may likely be armed.)
If you see the man in this picture,
please immediately contact the police.
Sir.
Your and Kaye’s phones are being tracked.
You won’t get away.
I turned my phone off.
No one will know we’re here.
Tell me, Nop.
Who’s behind this?
I’m not playing, Nop.
I’m sorry, sir.
I didn’t want to do any of this.
But I had no choice.
The forensic team,
the coroner responsible for the autopsy,
they made sure all the evidence
was staged to help the case…
Kaye won’t get away with it, Inspector.
How the hell did that happen?
I don’t know, sir!
Someone really important
must have his back.
Inspector…
If I refused to play along,
it wouldn’t be just me they go after…
It would be my parents.
I understand you, Nop.
I’ll handle all this.
I don’t care which big shot is behind it.
I trust you, sir.
I have a video.
(I know no evidence I have
will be worth anything against Kitti.)
It’s done, sir.
(This is my trump card.)
(It’s my leverage
in case things go south,)
(I’ll still have a way out.)
Then I’ll use that video you took
to take them all down.
If you’re going to fight,
I’ll fight alongside you, sir.
(Sorry, the number you have dialed
cannot be reached at this time.)
(Hello, dai-sensei.)
(Nekros is finally coming to an end.)
(I wonder if your ending and mine
will be the same, dai-sensei.)
(I want you to decide how the end
for the last victim should be.)
(Just draw it.)
(I’ll take care of the rest.)
PHAT
(Sorry, the number you have dialed
cannot be reached—)
(I’m on my way.)
Inspector.
The stingray caught the signal
from the suspect’s sim.
There was outgoing traffic 10 seconds ago.
It was a text.
The suspect has turned off
his phone, though.
It’s too late for him anyway.
Can you pinpoint where the text was sent?
Of course, sir.
(To all units, the suspect’s location
has been confirmed.)
(Inspector Kitti’s team
is heading there to make an arrest.)
(In case of resistance, drastic measures
are allowed to bring him in.)
Inspector.
They know where Kaye is now.
Take your video to my uncle.
Don’t stop by anywhere.
And send me Kaye’s coordinates.
I’ll be there.
Yes, sir.
He’s a serial killer.
We’ll take him in dead or alive.
Yes, sir. Let’s go.
Hurry up!
Come on!
Halt!
Hey!
I said halt!
Stop!
Kaye, I said stop!
Come with me.
Stop!
Secure all exits.
Leave no stones unturned.
You’re all allowed to shoot on sight.
Stay close to me.
Halt!
Drop your weapon.
We won’t spare you even despite
your connection to your uncle.
Do you plan to kill me and Kaye
and set this up as self-defense?
That’s not very thorough of you.
It may not be thorough but it will work.
The serial killer Nekros
and the police officer resisting arrest,
no matter how it’s written in the report,
it will be believable.
It sounds like it might work.
Unfortunately I have a video…
of you kidnapping Kaye
to set him up for a murder.
I’m sure you know what I’m talking about.
So if anything happens to me and Kaye,
Nop is sending that video straight
to the special investigative task force.
All of you should consider this carefully.
Your boss here is backed
by someone powerful.
He’ll make it.
But the rest of you, maybe not.
You’re all in the video, right?
Do you want to take the blame
and go to jail for life for his sake?
Think carefully.
You’re bluffing.
I control the forensic team.
I control how the report is written.
It was my order
to put Kaye’s fingerprints on that hammer.
And so what?
I control everything.
That kind of stupid evidence
won’t hurt me.
Did you hear that, Uncle?
It just so happened that I’m on the phone
with my Uncle Chaiwat.
Oh…
So is the SWAT team, by the way.
You confessed the whole thing, too.
Halt!
Put down your weapons.
Put down your guns.
Put them down.
Put your hands up.
(I don’t think Kitti is capable
of doing something like this.)
(Are you sure about this, Phat?)
Please trust me this once, Uncle.
Nop has a video
that Kitti can’t get away with.
Nop’s bringing you that video.
No matter how powerful Kitti’s boss is,
I’m dragging him out into the light.
(If you’re sure about this,
I’ll help you.)
Don’t think your uncle
will save you every time.
This isn’t over.
That’s good.
I’d love to know
if your boss is bigger than the laws.
Take him.
We have evidence now that Kitti was trying
to make you take the blame for this.
He was rearranging the old case files
and planting evidence to frame you.
All the evidence is going to
a special investigative team.
You can breathe now.
Phat.
I…
Thank you.
For not abandoning me.
I told you.
If I agree to help you,
I’ll help you till the end.
But you have to stop
putting yourself at risk like this.
Even if I had a hundred lives,
I’d have to spend all those lives
saving you.
Sir.
The file is locked
due to brute-force protection.
If we get the password wrong five times,
the file will delete itself.
It’s unsalvageable.
Find a different way to decipher the code.
That’s doable.
But it will take so much time.
And the longer we take,
the riskier it will be.
I believe he’s challenging me.
What does that mean?
Asura gave me the right
to decide the ending.
Which means I, as the creator,
am the only person who knows the password.
Can I try something?
Sure.
Maybe…
The date of the first chapter publication?
It’s incorrect.
Calm down. Take your time thinking.
Asura went to all this trouble
to lure you into that abandoned building.
He left a whole laptop there.
That means his goal is for you
to see the ending he has planned.
You’re right.
There’s no way the password
could be too complex.
It has to be something you can guess.
And it must be something
only you and he know.
I really can’t believe Kitti
would pull something like this.
There must be a reason he would even dare.
Maybe he was hired by someone.
We have to get it out of him.
This is the request
for his provisional release.
Yes.
Sir.
His provisional release
has been authorized.
Release?
How?
The evidence is obviously against him.
There’s even a confession.
On what basis is he released?
What you claimed as his confession
is not practical for the case.
Inspector Kitti was on duty at the time.
What he said was a negotiation technique
called ‘roleplay.’
He was roleplaying as a dirty cop
to trick you, Inspector Phat,
who was protecting the suspect,
to put your gun down.
As for the evidence…
I never received any evidence, sir.
That can’t be true.
I specifically asked Nop
to hand that video
to the special investigative team
yesterday.
I really never received anything, sir.
So there is no evidence.
Excuse me, sir.
I think something is getting fishy.
You should contact Nop right away.
Are you sure you can trust him?
Phat, what does this mean?
I just heard Kitti
has been released on bail.
What?
Nop never handed that video in.
The case officer never received anything.
I’ve been calling him
and he’s not answering.
Shit.
I should have known that.
He’s a coward.
He’d run with his tail between his legs.
Hold on.
Think for a moment.
Nop has no reason to do that.
If Nop didn’t betray us,
that means…
They knew Nop had that evidence.
(Phat.)
Yes, Uncle?
(We found him.)
You found Nop?
POLICE FORENSIC SCIENCE
Is that a celebrity’s autograph, sir?
Right on your back.
That must be so damn exclusive.
Wait!
Isn’t that you, Inspector?
Oh!
Mr. Kaye!
He’s the guy whose autograph
was on your jacket that day!
Oh, Inspector.
Why didn’t you tell me
you’re into that kind of manga?
Who’d have thought
from your usual smolder?
Surprise!
Welcome back to work, Inspector.
I trust you, sir.
If you’re going to fight,
I’ll fight alongside you, sir.
Oh?
Inspector.
Mr. Kaye.
What are you two doing out here all alone?
I’ll be right back in.
No, hold on.
Let me take a photo.
Y’all look so distant.
Can you move in a little?
Just like that.
It doesn’t work, Mr. Kaye.
-Closer.
-How about this?
Now we’re talking.
Sir, you gotta smile a little.
Smile, you know?
Smile.
Alright.
One, two, three.
Got it.
Can I get a selfie?
Come on.
One, two, three.
If you keep going like this,
you could be their next victim.
What a perfect time to be back.
I have a fun job for you.
I’m sure you’ll like it.
What can the stupid laws
do against these jerks?
Someone who’s never been hurt like you
would never understand.
It’s not the case I’m worried about.
What are you worried about, then?
You.
We’re all looking forward
to seeing how Nekros ends.
Maybe the ending is right where
the beginning is.
Am I right, dai-sensei?